Zahid Hussain



zahid4453@gmail.com



+92 3077170871



linkedin.com/in/zahid-hussain-8a0b0511a



https://zahidhussain.tech

Summary

As a PHP Laravel Engineer, I specialize in designing and developing high-quality web applications using the Laravel PHP framework.

5+ years of experience as a PHP Laravel Engineer

Specialize in designing and developing high-quality web applications using the Laravel PHP framework Strong understanding of including HTTP protocols, RESTful APIs

Experience with front-end technologies, including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, as well as version control systems, such as Git, and databases, including MySQL

Collaborative team player with strong problem-solving skills and ability to adapt to changing requirements and priorities

Experience



Software Engineer

Medusa Labs

Feb 2021 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Designing and developing web applications using Laravel PHP framework

Writing clean and maintainable code to ensure high-quality standards

Debugging and troubleshooting issues with applications

Creating and maintaining technical documentation

Collaborating with cross-functional teams to ensure seamless project delivery

Staying up-to-date with the latest industry trends and technologies to improve efficiency and productivity

Web Developer

Avialdo Solutions

May 2019 - Present (4 years 1 month)

Php Laravel Developer, Maintain web applications, create rest API's, and create new web systems by using Core Php and Laravel, Bootstrap, Javascript, Jquery, Mysql, Postgress.



Web Developer

CN Digital Solutions

Jan 2018 - May 2019 (1 year 5 months)

Education



University of Sindh

2013 - 2016

Skills

Laravel • PHP • SQL • Software Development • ¡Query • Bootstrap • Vue.js • Django